About Me

I am Stefanos Michael, a person really passionate with technology and science. I get involved into technology events and I've co-founded Brainstorm. I am a former Microsoft Student Partner and a student member to various tech-related organizations, such as IEEE and StudentGuru Patras. The last two years as a student, I've started to get interested in Robotics, Artificial Intelligence and the Internet of Things, so I started my thesis on "Collection of information & sensor control in a residential environment".

Languages I speak



Greek - Native



English - IGCSE (Grade B)

Work Experience

FreeeWiFi Cyprus July 2017 - present

Network Engineer

Develop and setup WiFi hotspots to provide Internet via captive portals for various companies.

iWP & Brand Building July 2017 - present

Web Developer

Design and develop responsive and dynamic websites for various companies

Brainstorm July 2011 - present

Co-Founder and Developer

Brainstorm is a company focused on making quality mobile apps and games for the Windows and Windows Phone platform, Brainstorm has a variety of hit-apps like the puzzle game Illuminate and the minimalistic text editor Write.

Microsoft Hellas September 2012 - September 2015

Student Partner

The main responsibilities of being a Microsoft Student Partner are to organize events, seminars and trainings at the University, to promote the company's tools and technologies and to be the contact point between professors, students and the company.

National Guard July 2008 - July 2010

Infantry Sergeant

I've served my country as an Infantry Sergeant with an Anti-Tank Specialty and I've also been an office assistant in "Millitary Education & Information Office".



STEFANOS MICHAEL Electrical & Computer Engineer

Paralimni, Cyprus

17/05/1990

DATE OF BIRTH

15+
PROJECTS
DELIVERED







Skills

Get in touch:

■ stefanos990@outlook.com

stefanos990.com

facebook.com/stefanos990

twitter.com/stefanos990

linkedin.com/in/stefanos990

Education

University of Patras September 2010 - July 2016

Department - Electrical & Computer Engineering

Master's equivalent studies (300 ECTS)

Thesis - Collection of information and sensor control in a residential environment \mathbf{GPA} - 7.64 / 10.00

Paralimni Lyceum (High School) September 2005 - June 2008

GPA - 19.75 / 20.00

Organizations

ETEK December 2016 - present

Member

The Cyprus Scientific and Technical Chamber (ETEK) is the statutory Technical Advisor to the State and is the umbrella organisation for all Cypriot Engineers. It was established by Law 224/1990 and is a Public Law Body with an elected Governing Body.

IEEE January 2011 - September 2015

Student Member

IEEE is the world's largest professional association dedicated to advancing technological innovation and excellence for the benefit of humanity. IEEE and its members inspire a global community through IEEE's highly cited publications, conferences, technology standards, and professional and educational activities.

StudentGuru Patras September 2012 - September 2015

Member

StudentGuru Patras is the first academic community in University of Patras majoring in Microsoft .NET related technologies. It was founded in October 2009 and its main vision is to bring students closer to popular technologies.

Skills and Personal Attributes





STEFANOS MICHAEL
Electrical & Computer Engineer

Paralimni, Cyprus

17/05/1990

DATE OF BIRTH

15+
PROJECTS
DELIVERED

About Me

Work Experience

Education

Skills

Get in touch:

■ stefanos990@outlook.com

stefanos990.com

facebook.com/stefanos990

twitter.com/stefanos990linkedin.com/in/stefanos990